We are three people of the same age!
We are 23 years old!
That's right!
Barbecue!
Bye-bye?
Listen!
Oh, no, no, no, no!
I totally blurred it out!
Ready!
Mashburrow.
Hey!
What do you mean, no?
What? I'm scared!
Please!
Hello everyone. I'm Moe Kanisawa, Mirei Suganami, and Kisaya Umise of Not Equal Me.
Here we go. It's a beautiful day today and I can hear the rain and dripping sound very much.
It is cool.
So, the three of us are the same age group.
Twenty-three years old. That's right. This is actually the first time for us to do this shoot as a same age group. I was really looking forward to it.
Speaking of summer, here is today's photo shoot.
Please take a look.
A barbecue with a little bit of water in it.
Yay!
Bamboo, bamboo.
That's right. I wanted to try it at home.
I'm glad. And barbecue.
Um, you know, I went shopping earlier, right?
Yes, we did.
So, the three of us will have fun today.
Yes, yes. I'll do my best.
I'd like to start the Nagashi Somen Noodle Flow right away. Yay!
I'm going to start the sink. Yay!
I'm going to rotate between eating, eating, eating.
By the way, do you both like Soumen? I love it!
I love it!
Thank you.
Don't make it too messy.
Sure thing.Indeed.
It's very white.
It is white.
The same age group is famous for spilling.
That's right.
Green onion, myoga, ginger, wasabi.
Amazing.
I like myoga.
You like myoga?
I love it.
Yay!
Looks delicious.
Do you want some ginger?
I don't mind. Thank you.
Thank you.
Then, Moe-chan will take care of it for you.
Sounds fun.
I'll practice.
Okay.
That's great.
Okay, perfect.
The goal is...
Saya takes so much that Mirutan won't eat it.
That's right.
That's the goal.
Oh, shit! Here she comes!
Go!
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on!
Accelerate, accelerate, accelerate!
Take it, take it, take it! My somen!
Ah! But it's a little bit stuck!
How is it?
Is it good?
Let's drink some miso.
Mmm! It's so good! I'm feeling summer!Mmmm! It's so good! I'm feeling summer!
I feel summer!
Let's go!
Next, the miretan!
Yay!
Nittama!
Ah! Nitama's here! Miretan!
Here it comes!
It's coming in really fast!
Aah!
Aah! Oh, no, no, no! Miretan! Miretan!
It's flowing!
This is so much fun!
It's delicious! It's so good! Delicious?
There's so much more! More!
Really?
Let's pour it all out!
Yes!
Here we go!
Yum!
Oh, my gosh!
Here it comes!
You're so cute! You look adorable!
What? It's slowing down a little bit!
Miretan! Miretan! Wait! We've gone too far!
We've gone too far!
Wait! Wait!
Ah! Perth!
It's gone!
Too much flow!
But, oh, well, well...
I didn't know it was so much fun to pour it in.
So much fun!
Next time...
I'd like to casually
I'd like to try a little wakame seaweed next time!
I'm so happy!I'm so happy!
We won!
Go!
This is bad!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
They like plums, too.
Wait a minute.
Wait, wait, wait!
It's coming! It's coming!
Oh, no!
Ume!
Wow!
Oh!
Plums!
Oh, I see... Nagashi Somen also has plums!
I didn't know that.
How is it? How does it taste?
The plums are good too.
Tasty?
I'm eating wakame, too.
It's good.
Wow, wakame and ume in the water.
That was amazing.
Now, I'd like to continue with the sink.
Actually, I've sped it up a bit.
Here we go!
Oh, good!
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Bye-bye.
Bye-bye?
Go, go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I totally missed it.
Come on.Come on!
They keep coming.
Sparta.
There they go, there they go.
What's happening so fast? Miretan's.
How's it coming?
Oh, but...
It's good.
You're getting it.
Are you eating?
He took the bird.
Not yet.
Don't flush it yet.
It's so good.
It's so good with ice.
Okay, then.
I'm going to get some wakame.
Kameron!
Eat and Burn.
How's it going? Wakame.
Don't say "wakame" all of a sudden.
He's saying something.
Oh, really?
It's a little too wakame. I can't taste it.
How about it? Do you have noodles?
No, I don't have any noodles.
I'm coming.
You're very fast, Mirei.
What are you going to do?
Go, go!
I'll be back in a bit.
Oh, okay!
Wait, it's so long to get it!
Maybe I'm not very good at it.
Wait, let's switch places.
Don't answer it!
Moe, Moe, Moe!
Moe, Moe, Moe, let's go!Moe, Moe, let's go.
Wait, this is a lot of stuff!
Miru no!
Miru-saaan!
It's too much!
Whoa, whoa!
You're good at grabbing things.
Really?
Actually, I sped it up a bit.
Oh, yeah?
More water?
Yeah, I think so.
That's why.
Hey, but there's a big drop.
What?
He's saying goodbye.
You're saying good-bye?
I think I'm gonna make two servings.
I'll take care of that later, too.
Okay, I'll eat it later.
Wait, last one then?
Last, but not least.
Last time? Okay, one last thing.
What do you mean, a little bit?
Okay, here we go.
Oh, man, there's a lot of them.
Good luck, Moe!
Hang in there.
I'll be there.
Wait, wait, wait!
He's gone!
Moe, that busted dragon
Hang on, it's going
Wait, wait, wait! Wait, wait, wait!
Eat half!
I got about two zeroes.
It's good. It's fun!
Long-lasting somen is so much fun!Nagai Somen is so much fun!
Then we will have a barbecue!
Nagai Somen was fun! We put in so many!
The main dish is ready!
I would like to introduce you to some of the shopping I did!
Let's go!
It's big because I went to Costco.
It was my first time to go to Costco, and my face, and the ingredients.
The bag is big too.
So, let's have a barbecue, but first, potato chips.
Let's start with the meat.
We love beef tongue.
Hey, there's a lot of meat.
It's all-you-can-eat.
We eat a lot.
Yakiniku.
Yakiniku?
Barra?
Wagyu.
It is Japanese black beef.
And sausages.
A lot of sausages.
Three kinds.
Amazing.
I also bought vegetables.
I bought some vegetables.
Bell peppers.
Shiitake mushrooms.
And...
Heavy.
Onions.
What should we do with them?
This is bad.
This is the biggest area you'll ever see.
It says 5 kilos, right?
Five kilos.
And you see that?Also, see?
Here it is.
Yolo-otoma.
Marshmallows from the supermarket.
And let's have some fun baking marshmallows!
Let's have fun baking marshmallows!
Emily, this is what we wanted.
And here are the potatos we've been craving.
And this too... because Korean seaweed goes with yakiniku.
Wait a minute. It's about the size of my torso.
Wow, that's like three sideburns.
Really? I'm so happy.
A turret! A girl's turret!
This is definitely good barbecue. I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
All right, let's cut to the chase.
What shall we do first?
Okay.
We've got three onions.
We're gonna split up the onions, right?
One to chop, one to peel.
I think we only need one.
One is fine.
There's a lot more.
Okay, let's stop.
Let's get some more.
There's green peppers, too.
I think they've been rustled.
Something here.
Maybe it'll be easier to peel if I cut here and here.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Let's go.
How much experience do you all have in cooking?
Not much, but...
You've gone quiet all of a sudden.
I didn't know you were that energetic.
Not much.Not much.
Moe is peeling a green bell pepper.
He's peeling the green pepper!
He's peeling!
It's okay. It's okay.
I cut them in half.
What?
It's okay.
It's okay if you eat it.
Sorry, onion.
I thought...
Now I can't do it. Part of
car
Basic tree Spark
Pareto
What happens when we get here
are
Let's do it!
A fine hakata troval teng but something but shaving street
It's big
What if we cut it like this?
I think it will look good.
There are so many ways to cut it.
What? No!
No!
This is not what we're looking for.
What? Want to try making curry?
What?
What? Wait, this?
Wait.
Oh, I'm coming! Come on, come on, come on, come on!
It's so good! It's so good!
That's it! That's it!
That's it! It's good!
Let's cut some shiitake mushrooms!
Is that shiitake mushrooms we're cutting?
Isn't that it? You know, the handle.Isn't that it? That's the handle.
Oh, really?
Oh, my God!
Wow! Wow!
You look like my mom!
I've never seen that before!
It looks like an umbrella!
That's amazing!
It's kind of bruised!
And it's raining!
I gotta go!
Oh!
Valley!
Tani's cutting!
Tani!
Oh, this much?
I don't see that much!
OK!
That's good!
Ha! Don't say that!
She was trying to cut it off!
She really did it!
I can't open it!
Stop it!
I'm worried.
You can cut it.
Oh, OK.
Thank you.
Wait a minute. I'm afraid of the red stuff.
Okay. Okay, let's go.
Yay. Here we go.
Here we go.
Everyone else is eating, too,
Sure thing.
Let's eat together and enjoy the view.
Great. Maybe while barbecuing.Good. Like while barbecuing.
Oh, sure.
Let me take it on the big screen.
Let's go.
Hey! Ei! Ei!
About two each? Yes, about two at a time.
At first.
This is the beef tongue zone. OK!
Yes!
Let's go, Momochan.
Momochan, are you a little awkward?
Come on!
I don't know, maybe a little sausage.
The sausage and the green bell pepper are a little bit...
They're sticking together!
They're sticking together! What do I do?
They're all stuck together!
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What do you want me to do?
Do you want me to pull it?
It's hot!
Are you okay?
Oh, no!
No!
You want to win?
Let's switch players.
We're doing it in threes? This is...
That's great.
Ah!
Let's see here.
It's kind of hot, hot, hot.
What's that?
Use it harder.
It's kind of distorted.
Now that it's done, let's eat!
Ready, go!
Yay! So many colors!Yay! So many colors!
I'm so happy!
So many colors! Lots of seasonings! Lemon and beef tongue go together! It's the best!
Beef tongue and lemon!
Let's open it!
Wow! Delicious!
Please, Moe! A delicious barbecue memorial!
With everyone in the same age group! Ready, set, go! Cheers!
Kampai!
New plates!
I'm so happy!
I want one for sure!
We cut them up in advance because we knew we'd spill them!
Oh, yeah.
You guys want to go?
Sure, of course.
Yes!
Yum! So soft!
So tender!
We grilled the meat ourselves, so it's kind of
It's the best!
The best?
Best?
No, it's not!
I've never heard of the best!
What's the best?
Hey, hey, what is it?
It's the same!
Yum!
Yummy grilled eel!
The grilled eel is delicious!
Surprise!
It's the same.
Oh my God!
It's so chaotic today.
I'll do my best!
Okay.one of the seven
Mash barrow!
Ya!
What are you doing?
I'm scared!
Please!
Aaaaah!
Wait!
Aren't you scared?
What? Aren't you scared?
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
At Mae-chan's party.
I was laughing.
It only took a few seconds.
That's scary. That's sad.
It's sad.
Let's redo it. Can I take it back?
Sad. It's too soon. Let's take it back.
Ha-ha-ha...
Okay, let's get back on track. Ready?
Wooooo...
Marshmallow... Yaaaah!
How long do I have to do this?
How long can I put the mask on?
Oh, but, you know, it's colored.
Oh, my God.
It's just a little bit away from burning.
It burns really badly here.
It's a little puffy.
It's cute.
Oh, that's good!
Do you think it's hot?
Looks hot!
It's getting bigger.
He's so cute.That's so cute.
You're good.
It's like a fox color.
Looks delicious.
Looks good!
Is it hot?
It's hot, for sure.
I'm scared.
And it's iron.
It's iron here!
That's scary.
Don't blow out the marshmallows.
It's kind of wobbly.
What is that? I have to blow it out.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Is it hot? Are you okay?
Wow!
Yum!
Oh, my God!
Is it hot?
Oh, really?
Marshmallow, you were the last one to feel sick.
You're in shape?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Wait! Yum!
I'm falling.
I just lifted it up a little bit.
Bon appétit.
Wow! Delicious!
Okay, here we go.
Ah!
Marshmallows are the best!
Mmm!
Mmm! Delicious!Yum! Delicious!
Sweet territory!
Wow! Oh, my goodness!
It's slippery!
It's so slippery!
It's so good!
This is so good!
Yeah!
It's so good!
Yum!
That was so much fun!
It was so much fun!
There were so many incidents!
It's just...! We are always the oldest and the three oldest sisters in the group, but...
I wonder if you could feel our usual atmosphere today?
Did you get it?
Yes!
It was so much fun!
It was really fun!
I hope there will be a second video, so please watch this video a lot!
Please watch it!
Then you will see a lot more of the three of us!
Yay!
Thank you!
Bye bye!